Trail Mix-Up is a comedy, animation film directed by Barry Cook.
During a picnic, Baby Herman follows a beaver into a perilous
sawmill - with Roger Rabbit in frantic pursuit.
Roger Rabbit (voice), played by Charles Fleischer.
Jessica Rabbit (voice), played by Kathleen Turner.
Young Baby Herman / Mrs. Herman (voice), played by April Winchell.
Adult Baby Herman (voice), played by Lou Hirsch.
Droopy Dog (voice), played by Corey Burton.
Bear / Beaver (voice), played by Frank Welker.
Tom Mix (1880–1940) was an American motion picture actor, director,
and writer whose career spanned from 1910 to 1935.
During this time he appeared in 270 films and established
himself as the screen's most popular cowboy star.
Mix's flair for showmanship set the standard for later
cowboy heroes such as Gene Autry and Roy Rogers.
His horse Tony also became a celebrity who received his own fan mail.
Born in Pennsylvania, Mix served in the United States Army
before moving to the Oklahoma Territory in 1902.
Three years later, after working as a physical fitness instructor, bartender, and peace
officer, he was hired as a full-time cowboy for the Miller Brothers 101 Ranch.
Soon after, Mix established himself as the star
attraction of the Millers' Wild West Show.
In early 1910 Mix agreed to work as an actor and
wrangler for the Selig Polyscope Company.
Mix alternated between working in films and in Wild West shows until
1913 when he went into the film business full-time.
The following year he established his own production unit and
became a director and writer as well as an actor.
His films for Selig were usually one and two-reel shorts that initially emphasized humor in the tradition of Will
Rogers but eventually moved into action-oriented stories that displayed Mix's riding and stunting prowess.
In 1917 Mix left Selig and signed a contract with the Fox Film Corporation.
His earliest films for them were two-reel shorts but
within a year he switched to features.
During his peak period in the 1920s Mix appeared in action-packed westerns filled
with fights and chases which often showed him doing his own stunt work.
His films were also known for their location work in places such as
Arizona's Grand Canyon and Colorado's Royal Gorge.
Among the notable directors that he worked with during this time were John Ford,
Sidney Franklin, Jack Conway, George Marshall, and Roy William Neill.
His leading ladies included Louella Maxam, Colleen Moore, Esther
Ralston, Laura La Plante, Billie Dove and Clara Bow.
In 1928, after eleven years and 86 films with Fox, Mix moved
to FBO Pictures for a series of five films.
With the advent of sound, Mix abandoned his film career
and returned to working in Wild West shows.
He came back to films in 1932 for a series of nine sound features for Universal.
In 1935, he appeared in his final film, a 15-chapter serial for Mascot Pictures.
Mix died in an automobile accident in Arizona five years later.
On February 8, 1960, Mix was awarded a star on the Hollywood Walk of Fame.
In 1998, Mix's film Sky High was added to the National
Film Registry by the Library of Congress.
The film explores themes of camping, cartoon, bear, sawmill, geyser.
The tone is lighthearted.